### [iOps360](https://iops360.com/ "iOps360")

The Premiere Operations Suite for EMS, Fire And Police

Menu

Privacy Policy & Terms of Service & User Guidelines
===================================================

You are here: [Home](https://iops360.com/) » [What is iOps360](https://iops360.com/iops360/) » [About Us](https://iops360.com/iops360/about-us/) » Privacy Policy & Terms of Service & User Guidelines

**Privacy Policy**

**_This is our updated Privacy Policy that took effect on February 21, 2023._**

_Your privacy is critically important to us. At Brad Goodman Solutions, we have a few fundamental principles:_

* We are thoughtful about the personal information we ask you to provide and the personal information that we collect about you through the operation of our service.
* We store personal information for only as long as we have a reason to keep it.
* We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what information shared and permanently deleted.
* We aim for full transparency on how we gather, use, and share your personal information.

Below is Brad Goodman Solutions’ privacy policy, which incorporates and clarifies these principles.

**Who We Are and What This Policy Covers**

Brad Goodman Solutions created iOps360 which provides tools to you and your organization to help you do your job quickly and efficiently. Our mission is to combine all the tools you commonly use into one platform built on your suggestions.

This Privacy Policy applies to information that we collect about you when you use:

* Our websites (including iOps360.com and BradGoodmanSolutions.com);
* Our mobile applications (including the iOps360 app); and
* Other products and services that are available on or through our websites (including Google calendar sync platforms).

Throughout this Privacy Policy we’ll refer to our website, mobile applications and other products and services collectively as “Services.”  
Below we explain how we collect, use, and share information about you, along with the choices that you have with respect to that information.  
Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any of our products or services that have a separate privacy policy.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

**Information We Collect**

We only collect information about you if we have a reason to do so–for example, to provide our Services, to communicate with you, or to make our Services better.

We collect information in three ways: if and when you provide information to us, automatically through operating our services, and from outside sources. Let’s go over the information that we collect.

**_Information You Provide to Us_**

It’s probably no surprise that we collect information that you provide to us. The amount and type of information depends on the context and how we use the information. Here are some examples:

* **Basic Account Information:** We ask for basic information from you in order to set up your account. For example, we require individuals who sign up for a Brad Goodman Solutions account to provide your name, a login and email address–and that’s it. You may provide us with more information–like your phone number(s) and cell phone number–but we don’t require that information to create your account.
* **Public Profile Information:** If you have an account with us, we collect the information that you provide for your public profile. This public profile is only public to your organization and is not accessible to the general public or anyone outside your organization. Your public profile is just that–public–so please keep that in mind when deciding what information you would like to include.
* **Content Information:** Depending on the Services you use, you may also provide us with information about you in the content for your profile and features. For example, if you write a note with your leave request or availability that includes biographic information about you, we will have that information, and so will anyone with access to your approval of these items. This might be obvious to you…but it’s not to everyone!
* **Credentials:** We do not store credentials for other service providers that you provide – for example, when you authorize the Google Calendar sync. Your credentials as sent to Google which provides us with a token that allows changes to your calendar.
* **Communications with Us:** You may also provide us information when you respond to surveys, communicate with our engineers about a support question, or post a question about your site in our public forums.

**_Information We Collect Automatically_**

We also collect some information automatically:

* **Log Information:** Like most online service providers, we collect information that web browsers, mobile devices, and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, IP address, unique device identifiers, language preference, referring site, the date and time of access, operating system, and mobile network information. We collect log information when you use our Services–for example, when you create or make changes to your website on bradgoodmansolutions.com.
* **Usage Information:** We collect information about your usage of our Services. For example, we collect information about the actions that site administrators and users perform on a site–in other words, who did what, when and to what thing on a site (e.g., \[user name\] added availability for  \[time/date\]). We also collect information about what happens when you use our Services (e.g., page views, support document searches at bradgoodmansolutions.com, button clicks) along with information about your device (e.g., mobile screen size, name of cellular network, and mobile device manufacturer). We use this information to, for example, provide our Services to you, as well as get insights on how people use our Services, so we can make our Services better.
* **Location Information:** We may determine the approximate location of your device from your IP address. We collect and use this information to, for example, calculate how many people visit our Services from certain geographic regions.
* **Stored Information:** We may access information stored on your mobile device via our mobile app. We access this stored information through your device operating system’s permissions.  For example, if you give us permission to access the Brad Goodman Solutions database storage on your mobile device’s database, our Services may access the database stored on your device to make the application operate.
* **Information from Cookies & Other Technologies:** A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Brad Goodman Solutions uses cookies and other technologies to help us identify and track visitors, usage, and access preferences for our Services, as well as track and understand e-mail campaign effectiveness.

**_Information We Collect from Other Sources_**

We may also get information about you from other sources. For example, if you create or log into your Brad Goodman Solutions account through another service (like Google) we will receive information from that service (such as your username, and basic profile information) via the authorization procedures used by that service. The information we receive depends on which services you authorize and any options that are available.  Your agency also has the option to link your account to publicly accessible websites to verify your licenses and credentials.  We will make every attempt to link your profile correctly and it is your responsibility to inform your Administrators and/or Brad Goodman Solutions should your imported data be incorrect.

We may also get information from third party services about individuals who are not yet our users (…but we hope will be!), which we may use, for example, for marketing and advertising purposes.

**How We Use Information**

We use information about you as mentioned above and as follows:

* To provide our Services–for example, to set up and maintain your account, host your scheduling suite, and backup and restore your scheduling suite;
* To further develop our Services–for example by adding new features that we think our users will enjoy or will help them to create and manage their websites more efficiently;
* To monitor and analyze trends and better understand how users interact with our Services, which helps us improve our Services and make them easier to use;
* To monitor and protect the security of our Services, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities, fight spam, and protect the rights and property of Brad Goodman Solutions and others;
* To communicate with you about offers and promotions offered by Brad Goodman Solutions and others we think will be of interest to you, solicit your feedback, or keep you up to date on Brad Goodman Solutions and our products; and
* To personalize your experience using our Services, provide content recommendations.

**Sharing Information**

**_How We Share Information_**

We do not sell our users’ private personal information.  
We share information about you in the limited circumstances spelled out below and with appropriate safeguards on your privacy:

* **Subsidiaries, Employees, and Independent Contractors****:**We may disclose information about you to our subsidiaries, our employees, and individuals who are our independent contractors that need to know the information in order to help us provide our Services or to process the information on our behalf. We require our subsidiaries, employees, and independent contractors to follow this Privacy Policy for personal information that we share with them.
* **Third Party Vendor****s:**We may share information about you with third party vendors who need to know information about you in order to provide their services to us. This group includes vendors that help us provide our Services to you (like Google for calendar sync) and those that help us understand and enhance our Services (like analytics providers). We require vendors to agree to privacy commitments in order to share information with them.
* **As Required by Law:** We may disclose information about you in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request. For more information on how we respond to requests for information about bradgoodmansolutions.com users, please contact Brad Goodman.
* **To Protect Rights and Property:** We may disclose information about you when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Brad Goodman Solutions, third parties, or the public at large. For example, if we have a good faith belief that there is an imminent danger of death or serious physical injury, we may disclose information related to the emergency without delay.
* **Business Transfer****s:** In connection with any merger, sale of company assets, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company, or in the unlikely event that Brad Goodman Solutions goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would likely be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. If any of these events were to happen, this Privacy Policy would continue to apply to your information and the party receiving your information may continue to use your information, but only consistent with this Privacy Policy.
* **With Your Consent:** We may share and disclose information with your consent or at your direction. For example, we may share your information with third parties with which you authorize us to do so, such as the Google with our Google Calendar Sync feature.
* **Aggregated and De-Identified Information:** We may share information that has been aggregated or reasonably de-identified, so that the information could not reasonably be used to identify you. For instance, we may publish aggregate statistics about the use of our Services.
* **Published Support Requests****:** And if you send us a request (for example, via a support email or one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish that request in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

**_Information Shared Publicly_**

Information you share is not available outside your organization except for public information indexed by search engines or used by third parties. Please keep all of this in mind when deciding what you would like to share.

**Security**

While no online service is 100% secure, we work very hard to protect information about you against unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction, and take reasonable measures to do so.

**Choices**

You have several choices available when it comes to information about you:

* **Limit the Information that You Provide:** If you have an account with us, you can choose not to provide the optional account information. Please keep in mind that if you do not provide this information, certain features of our Services–for example, email and SMS notifications–may not be accessible.
* **Limit Access to Information On Your Mobile Device:** Your mobile device operating system should provide you with the ability to discontinue our ability to collect stored information or location information via our mobile apps. If you do so, you may not be able to use certain.
* **Opt-Out of Electronic Communications:** You may opt out of receiving promotional messages from us. Just follow the instructions in those messages. If you opt out of promotional messages, we may still send you other messages, like those about your account and legal notices.
* **Set Your Browser to Reject Cookies:** At this time, Brad Goodman Solutions does not respond to “do not track” signals across all of our Services. However, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies before using Brad Goodman Solutions’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of Brad Goodman Solutions’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Other Things You Should Know (Keep Reading!)**

**_Transferring Information_**

Brad Goodman Solutions is a worldwide service. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer, and storage of information in and to the U.S. and other countries, which may have rights and protections that are different from those in your home country.

**_Analytics Services Provided by Others_**

Other parties may provide analytics services via our Services. These analytics providers may set tracking technologies (like cookies) to collect information about your use of our Services and across other websites and online services. These technologies allow these third parties to recognize your device to compile information about you or others who use your device. This information allows us and other companies to, among other things, analyze and track usage, and determine the popularity of certain content.  Please note this Privacy Policy only covers the collection of information by Brad Goodman Solutions and does not cover the collection of information by any third party advertisers or analytics providers.

**_Third Party Software_**

If you’d like to use third party software like APIs, Google Calendar sync and Vehicle trackers, with our Services, please keep in mind that when you interact with them you may provide information about yourself to those third parties. We don’t own or control these third parties and they have their own rules about collection, use and sharing of information. You should review their rules and policies when installing and using third party software.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Brad Goodman Solutions may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. Brad Goodman Solutions encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the change log below, and, in some cases, we may provide additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you a notification through e-mail or your home page).  Your continued use of the Services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your consent to such change.

### Recent Posts

### Archives

Archives Select Month December 2024 November 2024 October 2024 July 2024 June 2024 May 2024 April 2024 January 2024 December 2023 November 2023 October 2023 September 2023 August 2023 July 2023 June 2023 May 2023 March 2023 February 2023 January 2023 December 2022 November 2022 October 2022 September 2022 August 2022 July 2022 June 2022 May 2022 April 2022 March 2022 February 2022 January 2022 December 2021 November 2021 October 2021 September 2021 August 2021 July 2021 June 2021 May 2021 April 2021 February 2021 December 2020 November 2020 October 2020 September 2020 August 2020 July 2020 June 2020 May 2020 April 2020 March 2020 February 2020 January 2020 December 2019 November 2019 October 2019 September 2019 August 2019 July 2019 June 2019 May 2019 April 2019 March 2019 February 2019 January 2019 December 2018 November 2018 October 2018 September 2018 August 2018 July 2018 June 2018 May 2018 April 2018 March 2018 January 2018 December 2017 November 2017 September 2017 August 2017 June 2017 May 2017 April 2017

### Categories

### Contact Info

* iOps360
* Sales & Support: (855) 811-0360
* Email: sales@iOps360.com
* Website: iOps360.com
* Offices: 109 East Debbie Dr, Shelby NC 28150

### Learn More

### Stay Connected

Copyright © 2024 [iOps360](https://iops360.com/ "iOps360"). All rights reserved. Theme [Spacious](https://themegrill.com/themes/spacious "Spacious") by ThemeGrill. Powered by: [WordPress](https://wordpress.org/ "WordPress").
